Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Personal Files, 1824-present UA.Personal.Files
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- E
  - Ebitz, Curtis V.
  - Eck, Philip R.
  - Eckert, Charles
  - Eckert, William H.
  - Eckhardt, Robert G.
  - Eckstrom, Stephanie
  - Edelman, Barbara
  - Edelstone, Daniel
  - Edeson, Anne
  - Edgar, Harry H. *
  - Edgar, Robert F.
  - Edmonds, Mary P. *
  - Edmundowicz, Daniel
  - Edmundson, W. F.
  - Edwards, Goldie "Marigold"
  - Edwards, Harold (Dr.)
  - Edwards, James M.
  - Edwards, Judy
  - Edwards, Marigold A.
  - Edwards, Michael
  - Edwards, Ogden Matthias, Jr. (Dr.) *
  - Edwards, Robert
  - Edwards, William E. *
  - Effinger, Marta
  - Egerman, Karl
  - Egert, Eli S.
  - Eggers, Calvin W.
  - Eggers, Edward E.
  - Eghtesad, Bijan
  - Egmore, Frederic A. *
  - Egolf, Donald
  - Egorin, Merrill
  - Ehrbar, Tom
  - Ehrenberg, A. S. C. *
  - Eibling, David E.
  - Eichelberger, R. Tony
  - Eichenlaub, Genevieve
  - Eichler, Marie
  - Eigenbrode, Charles R.
  - Einstein, Albert *
  - Einstein, Elizabeth
  - Eisen, Martin M.
  - Eisenberg, Leon
  - Eisenhower, Dwight David *
  - Eisman, Milton (Dr.)
  - Eister, William D.
  - Elagin, Ivan (SEE Matveiv, Ivan)
  - Elbis, Elbert
  - Elder, Dave *
  - Elder, Max Q.
  - Eldridge, Larry, Jr.
  - Elkins, Carol Magdalene *
  - Elko, Brian
  - Ellenbogen, Eric
  - Eller, Andrew W.
  - Elliot, Gwen
  - Elliott, Charles
  - Elliott, B. Charles, Sr.
  - Elliott, Dan W.
  - Elliott, Emily
  - Elliott, John
  - Elliott, Virginia
  - Ellis, Brian
  - Ellis, David
  - Ellis, Demetrius *
  - Ellis, Kimberly
  - Ellis, Lawrence D. (Dr.)
  - Ellis, Raffee G. *
  - Ellison, Frank O. (Dr.)
  - Elm, Sandra
  - Elman, Nancy
  - Elmer, Elizabeth *
  - Elmer, Manuel *
  - Elovitz, Stuart
  - Elsbree, Oliver W. *
  - Else, Gerald F. (Prof.)
  - Elser, Arlon E. *
  - Elston, Catherine
  - Elterich, T. J. *
  - Elton, Geoffrey R. (Dr.)
  - Elvgren, Gillette
  - Emanuel, Lynn C.
  - Embertson, Mary Sue
  - Emig, W. H.
  - Endacott, Pamela
  - Engberg, Sandra
  - Engel, Bernard
  - Engel, David (oversize) *
  - Engel, Joe
  - Engel, Robert F.
  - Engelder, Carl J. *
  - Engelhardt, Fred
  - Engels, Eugene
  - England, Gerri
  - Englert, Edmund
  - Englesberg, Ellis (Dr.)
  - English, R. J.
  - English, William T.
  - Enick, Robert
  - Entenberg, Robert D. *
  - Enterline, Philip
  - Enwright, Parker
  - Epperson, David E. *
  - Epstein, Aubrey
  - Epstein, Herman T.
  - Epstein, Lawrence
  - Erbe, Arthur
  - Erdman, Peter W.
  - Erickson, Florence
  - Erikson, Erick H.
  - Erikson, Kai T.
  - Erkel, Todd
  - Erlen, Judith
  - Ermentrout, G. Bard
  - Ernick, Robert
  - Ernstoff, Marc
  - Eror, Nicholas G., Jr.
  - Eross, Bela
  - Ertel, Robert J.
  - Ersoz, Clara Jean
  - Ersoz, Namik *
  - Esch, Richard T.
  - Eshelman, M. Roger
  - Eshelman, Thomas *
  - Eskey, David Ellsworth
  - Esman, Milton J. (Dr.) *
  - Estep, James W.
  - Estevez, Miguel
  - Estrada, Nancy
  - Etheridge, Albert L.
  - Ethridge, Wendy
  - Etter, Lewis E. (Dr.)
  - Ettinger, Joel
  - Etzel, Gastao
  - Etzel, Kenneth R.
  - Euba, Akin
  - Evangelista, Nick
  - Evanko, James L.
  - Evanlcovich, Sandra
  - Evans, Amy
  - Evans, Betty L.
  - Evans, Bob *
  - Evans, Christopher
  - Evans, Emory Gibbons
  - Evans, George
  - Evans, K. James
  - Evans, John H., III
  - Evans, Kenneth
  - Evans, Nancy
  - Evans, Paul
  - Evans, Robert
  - Evans, Todd
  - Everett, Daniel L.
  - Everett, William G. (Dr.)
  - Evert, Walter H.
  - Evosevic, Bosanka (oversize)
  - Ewert, Kevin
  - Ewing, Alexander (class of 1835)
  - Ewing, W. H. *
- F
  - Fabian, Tanya
  - Fabian, Thomas
  - Fabio, Anthony
  - Fabrega, Horacio
  - Faddis, G. Elisabeth
  - Fadzen, Robert
  - Faget, Maxime A.
  - Fahey, George L. (Dr.) *
  - Fairfield, Erle *
  - Fairholm, Gilbert W.
  - Faison, Helen
  - Falco, Charles
  - Falk, Fanny Edel
  - Falk, Jim
  - Falk, Joel
  - Falk, Leon *
  - Falk, Lottie
  - Falk, Marjorie L.
  - Falk, Susannah
  - Falo, Louis D.
  - Falssenfeld, Susan
  - Fammartino, L. Keith
  - Fan, Zheng
  - Fang, Che
  - Fanzo, Michelle
  - Farber, Emmanuel (Dr.)
  - Farber, Karen
  - Farber, Stephen
  - Farmer, Fannie (SEE Perkins, Wilma)
  - Farmer, Jessie
  - Farmer, Randy L.
  - Farmer, William R.
  - Farner, David M.
  - Farnsworth, Norman R.
  - Farooqi, Naimur Rahman
  - Farrell, Christopher
  - Farris, Harold
  - Fasolka, Michael
  - Fass, Daniel
  - Fassio, Virgil
  - Fatyol, Robert
  - Fauconneau, Guy
  - Favorini, Attilio
  - Fazio, Foge
  - Feagan, Joe
  - Fear, Jerry J.
  - Fechter, Alan
  - Fechter, George A.
  - Fedder, Edwin
  - Fedel, Arthur
  - Fedele, John A.
  - Federle, Michael P.
  - Federspiel, William J.
  - Fedorochko, William, Jr.
  - Feghari, Carol A.
  - Fehroedel, Dale P. *
  - Feibelman, Walter
  - Feick, Lawrence
  - Feig, Konnilyn (Dr.)
  - Feingold, David S. (Dr.)
  - Feinstein, Karen Wolk
  - Feldman, Arthur
  - Feldman, Heidi
  - Feldman, Marvin J.
  - Feller, H. Richard
  - Fels, Eberhard
  - Felsenfeld, Gary
  - Felsenheld, Susan
  - Feng, Min
  - Fennell, Robert H. (Dr.)
  - Ferber, Daniel Arthur
  - Ferberber, Murray B. (Dr.)
  - Ferderbar, Joseph E.
  - Ferejohn, Michael
  - Ferguson, Albert B., Jr. *
  - Ferguson, Berrylin J.
  - Ferguson, Glenn *
  - Ferguson, Heather
  - Ferguson, Herb
  - Ferguson, Jean
  - Ferguson, John Maxwell *
  - Ferguson, Russell J. (oversize) *
  - Ferketish, B. Jean
  - Fernando, Chrish
  - Fernando, Quintus *
  - Ferree, N. Ferguson
  - Ferrell, Janet Noel *
  - Ferrell, Robert
  - Ferrero, Grace W.
  - Ferris, Josh
  - Ferson, Peter F. *
  - Fertman, Carl
  - Fesler, Wesley E.
  - Fessenden, Reginald A. *
  - Fetherston, Eleanor (Mrs.)
  - Fetterman, George H.*
  - Fetterman, John C. *
  - Fetterman, John C. (Mrs.) (SEE Stein, Margaret)
  - Feuer, Jane
  - Feynman, Win
  - Fichter, William
  - Ficke, John
  - Fickes, W. L. (Dr.)
  - Field, Melvin
  - Fielder, Earl *
  - Fields, Richard
  - Fiez, Julie
  - Figart-Helsen, Christine
  - Figueroa, Adrian
  - Figurel, J. Allen (Dr.) *
  - Filner, Joel B.
  - Finch, William R.
  - Finck, Henry (Dr.)
  - Finder, Jonathan
  - Fine, Michael J.
  - Finegold, David
  - Finegold, David N.
  - Finegold, Helene
  - Finegold, Marcella
  - Finegold, Wilfred J. (Dr.)
  - Fingeret, Jay
  - Fink, David
  - Fink, James
  - Fink, Mitchell
  - Fink, Joseph
  - Finkel, Mitchell S. *
  - Finkel, Steve
  - Finkelstein, Sydney
  - Finley, E. M. *
  - Finley, James
  - Finn, Frances M. *
  - Finn, Olivera
  - Finney, Theodore M. (oversize) *
  - Fiorentino, Lisa
  - Fireman, Philip
  - Firestone, Leonard *
  - Firestone, Nathan
  - Firestone, Steven C. *
  - Fiscante, Nick
  - Fischer, John L.
  - Fischer, N. Arthur
  - Fischer, Jon
  - Fischer, Katie
  - Fischer, Lori Ann
  - Fischer, Lucy
  - Fischer, Richard L.
  - Fischer, Willard G.
  - Fish, Lonny
  - Fisher, Alan *
  - Fisher, Bernard *
  - Fisher, Edwin R.
  - Fisher, Henry C.
  - Fisher, J. Bertram
  - Fisher, John J.
  - Fisher, Karen
  - Fisher, Linda
  - Fisher, Mike
  - Fisher, William G. *
  - Fishman, Victor A.
  - Fite, Wade *
  - Fithian, Edwin J.
  - Fitterer, Raymond *
  - Fitzgerald, Larry
  - Fitzgerald, Rufus H. (oversize) *
  - Fitzgerald, W. J.
  - Fitzpatrick, Thomas
  - Fitzpatrick, Timothy
  - Fitzsimmons, Ami L.
  - Fix, Jacqueline
  - Flack, Michael J. (Dr.) *
  - Flaherty, John P.
  - Flake, Sharon
  - Flamer, Erica
  - Flanagan, John C. *
  - Flanagan, Kathleen A.
  - Flechtner, Harry M.
  - Flecker, Sally Ann
  - Fleissner, Kathy
  - Fleming, Kenneth
  - Fleming, O. J.
  - Fleming, Robert D.
  - Fletcher, Dianne
  - Fletcher, James C. (oversize) *
  - Fletcher, Mildred *
  - Fletcher, Najuma
  - Fletcher, Ronald D.
  - Flew, Antony
  - Flickinger, John C. *
  - Flint, Camille
  - Flint, George M. (Dr.)
  - Flint, Norman K. *
  - Flocken, Ira G.
  - Florence, Virginia Proctor Powell
  - Flores, Stephen
  - Florez-Estrada, Nancy B.
  - Flory, Paul J. (Dr.)
  - Floyo, Thomas
  - Fluharty, Vernon L.
  - Flynn, Ida
  - Flynn, Joanne
  - Flynn, Roger R.
  - Flynn-Saldana, Kelly
  - Foa, Pamela
  - Foerster Family (Emil, Adolph, Norman)
  - Foerster, Thomas
  - Fogarty, Neal
  - Fohr, Samuel
  - Foldes, Francis
  - Foley, Thomas P.
  - Foley, Trevor
  - Folin, Elizabeth *
  - Folks, Edgar
  - Follansbee, Marcus A. *
  - Follansbee, William P.
  - Folman, Mordechai
  - Foltin, Lore B.
  - Fonseca, Fred
  - Foor, W. Eugene
  - Forbes, John *
  - Ford, Angela
  - Ford, Anthony *
  - Ford, Dennis
  - Ford, Diane E.
  - Ford, Henri R.
  - Ford, Henry P.
  - Ford, Henry "Model T"
  - Ford, Joyce A.
  - Forejt, David
  - Formella, Laura
  - Fornal, Justin
  - Forndorf, Frederick H.
  - Forni, Pier Massimo
  - Forrest, Edward J. *
  - Forsyth, Robert L.
  - Forsythe, Diana
  - Forsythe, Ronald J.
  - Forte, Melina
  - Forward, Walter
  - Foss, Megan
  - Foster, Angela
  - Foster, Genevieve
  - Foster, George V. (Dr.)
  - Foster, Henry H. "Harry"
  - Foster, Mollie Davidson
  - Foster, Stephen*
  - Foust, Mary
  - Foulke, Larry R.
  - Foulks, Gary
  - Fowler, Alexander
  - Fowler, George B. *
  - Fowler, Harry *
  - Fowler, Richard
  - Fowler, Talbert B.
  - Fox, Andrea
  - Fox, Cyril A., Jr.
  - Fox, John
  - Frader, Joel E.
  - Fraenkel, Gerd *
  - Fraley, Donald
  - Fralic, Bill
  - Fralic, Maryann F.
  - France, Richard
  - Francis, Anne
  - Francis, Sam *
  - Francis, Thomas
  - Franck, F.
  - Franhofer, Lisa
  - Frank, Andre G.
  - Frank, Ellen (Dr.)
  - Frank, Eric
  - Frank, Fred
  - Frank, Guido
  - Frank, Henry S. *
  - Frank, Isaac W.
  - Frank, Linda
  - Frank, Marietta
  - Frank, Nancy Newman
  - Franklin, Agnes
  - Franklin, Don
  - Franklin, Samuel P. (oversize) *
  - Franzen, Barbara
  - Franzen, James S. (Dr.)
  - Fraser, John (General)
  - Frasure, William Wayne *
  - Frazier, Renee
  - Frazier, William, Jr.
  - Fred, August R. (Dr.) *
  - Frederick, Kenneth Charles
  - Frederick, Richard G.
  - Frederick, Shirley
  - Frederick, William C.
  - Frederickson, A. F. *
  - Fredette, Barbara
  - Freeman, Bruce
  - Freeman, Jack E. *
  - Freeman, Jack E. (oversize)
  - Freeman, Linton
  - Freeman, Nino Maurice
  - Freeman, Tom
  - Freile, Alfonso *
  - Freiser, Henry
  - French, Jeanne
  - French, William
  - Frerotte, Jay
  - Freund, Paul A.
  - Frey, Albert W. *
  - Frezza, Christine
  - Friberg, Thomas R.
  - Frick, Helen C.
  - Frick, Henry Clay
  - Fried, Daisy
  - Fried, David Paul
  - Friede, Samuel A.
  - Friedberg, Joan Brest *
  - Friedman, L. (oversize) *
  - Friedman, Louis L.
  - Friedman, Michael
  - Friedman, Milton I.
  - Friedman, Ruth S.
  - Friesell, Frederick C.
  - Frieselle, H. Edmund *
  - Frieze, Irene
  - Frisch, Ragnar
  - Frisch, Ronald W.
  - Fritz, Julie
  - Frizzell, Raymond
  - Froehlich, Fritz *
  - Frolander-Ulf, Monica
  - Frolick, Lawrence
  - Fromm, Gerhard
  - Fronhofer, Carl
  - Fronhofer, Lisa
  - Frost, Albert Ellis *
  - Frost, Ellis Mills
  - Frost, Robert *
  - Fry, Edward
  - Fry, Harold L., Jr.
  - Frye, Nadine G. *
  - Frye, Reginald
  - Fryon, S. C.
  - Fryxell, David A.
  - Fu, Freddie
  - Fuchs, Carl
  - Fuchs, Franklin
  - Fuhrman, Carl
  - Fuhrman, Eileen
  - Fukuda, Yukihisa
  - Fuller, Dalyann
  - Fullerton, Ernest
  - Fulton, A. P. (class of 1826)
  - Fulton, Charles
  - Fulton, Paul F. *
  - Fulton, Robert
  - Fulwylie, Christine (oversize)
  - Funari, John
  - Fundenburg, Walter Hullihen
  - Funderburgh, James L.
  - Fung, John (Dr.)
  - Furey, Patricia
  - Furin, Bernadette
  - Furka, Deborah M.
  - Furlan, Ping
  - Furman, Joseph
  - Furtsch, Edward F.
  - Fusco, Margie
  - Futrell, William *
- G
  - Gabarda, Ana
  - Gabbaccia, Donna
  - Gabbert, Mont Robertson *
  - Gabbidon, Shaun
  - Gabell, Marcene P. *
  - Gaffey, Mark D.
  - Gaffius, Don
  - Gaffney, Paul (Dr.) *
  - Gage, J. Fred *
  - Gage. George W. *
  - Gaines, Billy
  - Gainor, Charles
  - Gainsford, Ronald *
  - Ganjanan, Shailendra
  - Galbraith, John (class of 1838)
  - Gale, Douglas
  - Gale, Richard
  - Gale, Robert L. *
  - Gallagher, Dave
  - Gallagher, Ed
  - Gallagher, Jere
  - Gallagher, Robert P. (Dr.)
  - Gallagher, Tess
  - Gallatin, Albert *
  - Gallion, Holly Harbage
  - Gal-Or, Benjamin
  - Gal-Or, Esther
  - Galvin, Thomas J. *
  - Gambee, Sumner
  - Gambotto, Andrea
  - Gamby, Raymond
  - Gammie, James
  - Gandhi, Natwar
  - Ganesh, Kulkarni Kishore
  - Ganley, Charles J.
  - Gaonkar, Dilip
  - Garber, Sharon
  - Garcia, C. Isaac
  - Garden, Jim
  - Gardeson, Pauline S. *
  - Gardner, James
  - Gardner, Joanne
  - Gardner, Mary
  - Gardner, William
  - Gareis, John W.
  - Garfinkel, Alan A.
  - Garfunkel, Myron
  - Gargis, Louise M.
  - Gargon, Frank
  - Garlen, J. Blake *
  - Garloch, Lorena *
  - Garman, Chris
  - Garman, Claudia
  - Garman, Noreen B.
  - Garner, Margaret D.
  - Garret, Margant E.
  - Garrison, Maxine (Mrs. William Schoyer) *
  - Garrison, William L. *
  - Garry, Ben
  - Garth, Joyce
  - Gartland, Ruth (oversize) *
  - Gartley, Rosanna
  - Gartner, J. Carlton, Jr. *
  - Garver, Kenneth (Dr.) *
  - Garvey, Charles Martin *
  - Gasinski, T. Z. *
  - Gaskins, William G., Jr.
  - Gasti, Nikki
  - Gates, Stephen
  - Gatewood, George
  - Gaul, Justin
  - Gaulin, Steven J. C.
  - Gault, Silas
  - Gauss, William F.
  - Gauthier, David
  - Gavaler, Judith S.
  - Gavin, Jonella
  - Gazala, Neven Abou
  - Gazzam, Edward D. (class of 1824)
  - Gazzam, Joseph P. *
  - Gazzaniga, Michael
  - Geary, Patricia
  - Geiger, Gene E.
  - Geiman, Alexander
  - Geise, Ben
  - Geise, John J. *
  - Geister, Carl H.
  - Gellatly, Kirstin
  - Geller, David
  - Gellin, John *
  - Gelman, Ruth
  - Generalovich, Brian
  - Gennes, Pierre-Giles de
  - Genge, William H. *
  - Genriari, Jeff
  - Gentile, Louis
  - Gentry, Steven E. *
  - George, Charles C.
  - George, Harold C.
  - George, Justine
  - George, Kathleen
  - George, Kenny
  - George, W. Arthur *
  - George, W. H. Krome
  - Georgescu, H. I.
  - Gerdes, John
  - Gerich, John
  - Gerjuoy, E. *
  - Gerlach, Jorg
  - Germano, Mike
  - Gerrero, Richard *
  - Gershon, Samuel
  - Gerstzen, Kristina
  - Gertenbach, Randy
  - Getzenberg, Robert
  - Geyer, Ellen M.
  - Gezon, Horrace M. (Dr.)
  - Ghanooni, Sion *
  - Ghivizzani, Steve
  - Giangarlo, Joyce
  - Giannotta, Frank
  - Giarratani, Frank
  - Gibbard, Allen F.
  - Gibbon, John
  - Gibbs, Lincoln R.
  - Gibbs, Robert
  - Gibson, Demond
  - Gibson, Donald
  - Gibson, Janet
  - Gibson, Janice *
  - Gibson, Karen
  - Gigliotti, Ron
  - Gigliotti, Tom
  - Gil, Joseph
  - Gilbert, Christopher
  - Gilbert, Robert
  - Gilbertson, John R.
  - Gilcher, Ronald O. (Dr.)
  - Gilchrist, Misty
  - Gilkey, So'Nia
  - Gill, Beth
  - Gill, Iris D.
  - Gill, Mary Kay
  - Gill, Mary Louise
  - Gill, Thomas, III
  - Gillespie, David L.
  - Gillespie, Harry, MD *
  - Gilliard, Tyrone
  - Gillin, John P. *
  - Gillman, Joseph
  - Gillott, Donald H.
  - Gillotti, Deborah
  - Gilmore, B. H.
  - Gilmore, Eugene Allen
  - Gilmore, John
  - Gingrich, Newt
  - Ginsburg, Mark
  - Giovengo, Annette L.
  - Giovinco, Justin
  - Girdany, Bertram R. *
  - Girshman, Karl M.
  - Gisler, Susan Rubisch
  - Gittins, Arthur *
  - Giulani, Michael J.
  - Givi, Peyman
  - Gjebre, Lisa
  - Glabicki, Paul *
  - Gladis, Michael
  - Glasco, Larry
  - Glasco, Lauren
  - Glaser, Alan A.
  - Glaser, Donald A.
  - Glaser, Robert
  - Glasser, Harriet Rose
  - Glazer, Walter S.
  - Gleason, E. Jeanne
  - Gleeson, Brian
  - Gleim, Jeff
  - Glenn, Edith Scott
  - Glenn, J. D. (class of 1846)
  - Glenn, Ronald
  - Glennan, Thomas K. (Dr.)
  - Glew, Robert Hayes
  - Gleynolds, L. F.
  - Glick, Ronald
  - Gloninger, Margaret
  - Glorioso, Joseph
  - Gluck, Martin R.
  - Glunt, J. Roger
  - Glunt, Roger D.
  - Glymour, Clark
  - Goddard, Maurice *
  - Godek, Andy
  - Godfrey, Daniel
  - Goenner, Betsy
  - Goff, Milton B. *
  - Goings, Nick
  - Gold, Barry
  - Gold, Bela *
  - Gold, Eric
  - Gold, Melanie
  - Goldberg, Bernard Z. *
  - Goldberg, Enid *
  - Goldberg, Marshall *
  - Goldberger, Anthony
  - Goldblatt, L. A.
  - Goldburg, Walter
  - Golden, Marita
  - Goldfarb, Ronald
  - Goldhammer, Robert
  - Goldman, Stanley *
  - Goldschmidt, Yadin Y.
  - Goldsmith, Albert Robin
  - Goldsmith, John
  - Goldsmith, Marilynn
  - Goldstein, Bernard D.
  - Goldstein, Bernard R.
  - Goldstein, Bruce
  - Goldstein, Donald (oversize)
  - Goldstein, Elizabeth
  - Goldstein. Linda
  - Golin, Barbara Anne Keefe
  - Golin, Stuart
  - Golla, Suman
  - Gollin, Susanne
  - Gondor, Jonathan
  - Gonsales, Ryan
  - Gonzalez, Pete
  - Gonzalez, Rene Miguel
  - Gonzalez-Arauzo, Angel
  - Good, Barbara
  - Good, Chester B.
  - Good, Ronald
  - Goodale, Stephen Lincoln *
  - Goode, John D. *
  - Goode, Malvin R.
  - Goodhart, Michael
  - Goodkind, Sara
  - Goodman, Robert M.
  - Goodpaster, Bret
  - Goodrich, Carter *
  - Goodwin, James G.
  - Gorcsan, John, III
  - Gordon, Adam
  - Gordon, Benjamin
  - Gordon, Donald E. (Dr.)
  - Gordon, George B.
  - Gordon, Gerd
  - Gordon, Harold J. (Dr.)
  - Gordon, Robert D. (Dr.) *
  - Gorelik, Eli
  - Gorham, Robert C. *
  - Gorin, Michael B.
  - Gorkin, Robin
  - Gormly, Thomas W.
  - Gornati, T. J.
  - Gornick, Mira
  - Gosfield, Amor
  - Goslen, Blake *
  - Goss, Frederic
  - Goss, James R.
  - Gostin, Lawrence
  - Gott, E. *
  - Gottfried, Bryon S. *
  - Gottfried, Mike
  - Gottlieb, Frederick
  - Gottlieb, Joan Eiger *
  - Gottman, Jean *
  - Gould, Andrew
  - Gould, David J. *
  - Gould, George (oversize) *
  - Gourley, David Tyler
  - Gow, J. Steele, Jr. *
  - Gow, J. Steele, Sr.
  - Grabe, Michael D.
  - Grabowski, Joseph
  - Grabowski, Paula
  - Grace, Anthony
  - Grandis, Jennifer Rubin
  - Grady, Dani
  - Grady, H. Roberts, Jr.
  - Grady, Janet
  - Graham, Charles
  - Graham, Christina L.
  - Graham, Eleanor G.
  - Graham, Jennifer
  - Graham, John *
  - Graham, Julian
  - Graham, Loren R.
  - Graham, Robert X. (oversize) *
  - Gramlich, Russell J.
  - Grandis, Jennifer R.
  - Granieri, Evelyn C.
  - Grant, Jack
  - Grant, John H. *
  - Graper, Elmer D. (Dr.) *
  - Gratton, Mercer A.
  - Grauer, David
  - Grave, Ilan
  - Graver, Victor A.
  - Gray, Aaron
  - Gray, D. S.
  - Gray, James F. *
  - Gray, Jennifer
  - Gray, J. Stanley
  - Gray, Peter (oversize) *
  - Greco, Joseph Vittorio
  - Grecco, William Louis (oversize) *
  - Greek, Ray
  - Green, Bill
  - Green, Donald M.
  - Green, Goerge R.
  - Green, Hugh (oversize)
  - Green, James F., Captain
  - Green, Mary H.
  - Green, Michael
  - Green, Richard
  - Green, Stephen W.
  - Greenamyre, J. Timothy
  - Greenberg, Janelle
  - Greenberg, Suzanne
  - Greene, Douglas A. *
  - Greene, Flint
  - Greene, James H.
  - Greene, William *
  - Greenfield, Sayre
  - Greeno, James
  - Greenspan, Robert Stephen
  - Greenspan, Susan
  - Greenwald, Maurine
  - Greenwood, Ernst (Dr.) *
  - Greer, Ricardo
  - Gregg, Frank
  - Gregg, Grace
  - Gregg, Lucien A. (Dr.)
  - Gregorian, Vartan
  - Gregory, James F. *
  - Greider, H. W.
  - Greis, Pat
  - Grettie, Donald P.
  - Grenvik, Anke, MD
  - Grever, Michael R.
  - Grey, Sarah
  - Grieco, Paul A.
  - Grier, Beatrice J.
  - Grier, G. W.
  - Grier, Norman McDowell (Dr.)
  - Grier, Robert "Bobby" *
  - Grier, Willa
  - Griffin, C. E.
  - Griffin, Lawrence E.
  - Griffin, Herschel E.
  - Griffin, Michael
  - Griffith, Bartley P.
  - Griffith, Este
  - Griffith, John Perry *
  - Griffiths, Jose-Marie
  - Griffiths, Paul E.
  - Griffiths, Robert E., Jr. *
  - Grigaliunas, Algis
  - Griggs, Joseph Franklin
  - Griggs, Robert F. (oversize) *
  - Grim, Latef
  - Grimes, Carroll
  - Grimes, Ronald
  - Grimm, Donald
  - Grindel, Scott
  - Grischow, Andrew
  - Griswold, Robert *
  - Groark, Christina
  - Groch, John
  - Groen, Frances K.
  - Grogan, Claudia Ellen
  - Grondahl, Mika
  - Gronenborn, Angela M.
  - Groover, Tonya
  - Grose, C. Herman *
  - Gross, Alvin C., Jr. "Skip"
  - Gross, Greg
  - Gross, Michael A.
  - Gross, Rhonda I.
  - Grossman, Burt
  - Grossman, Charles C., MD
  - Grossman, Zvi
  - Grove, John J.
  - Grove, Nancy C.
  - Grove, William R. (oversize) *
  - Grubbs, Robert
  - Grube, Beth
  - Grube, Mike
  - Gruener, Harry J.
  - Grufferman, Seymour (Dr.)
  - Grunbaum, Adolph *
  - Grundstein, Nathan D.
  - Grunnagle, Jerome F. (Dr.)
  - Grunstra, Neale S.
  - Gruse, W. A.
  - Gualtierotti, Torquato
  - Guang, Pan
  - Gubar, Marah
  - Guckes, Amy Anne
  - Guernsey, Bridget
  - Guevara, Peter A. *
  - Guggenheimer, James (Dr.) *
  - Guillen, Jorge
  - Guise, Olivier
  - Gulbransen, Margery
  - Gullion, Beatrice S. (oversize) *
  - Gullion, Wendell
  - Gundelfinger, George F.
  - Gundlach, Kate
  - Gungor, Anil
  - Gunkle, Ed
  - Gunnerson, Helena B. *
  - Gupta, Anil K.
  - Gupta, Om P. (Dr.)
  - Gupta, Phalguni
  - Gupta, Shenu
  - Gur, David
  - Gurtin, Lee
  - Guss, Mike
  - Gustafson, Andy
  - Gustine, Frank
  - Guterman, Jeffrey C.
  - Gutherie, Robert
  - Guthrie, Charles *
  - Guthrie, John A.
  - Guthrie, George W. *
  - Guthrie, Robert V. (Dr.) *
  - Gutierrez, Gitanjali
  - Gutkind, Lee
  - Gutwirth, Marc R.
  - Guy, J. F.
  - Guydosh, Gary
  - Guzick, David
  - Guzman, Ana
  - Gyorgyi, Denes *
  - Gyure, James
- H
  - Haar, Jackie
  - Haas, Eugene George
  - Haas, Kenneth Brooks
  - Haas, Missa
  - Hackett, Jon
  - Hackett, Paul
  - Hackworth, Steven
  - Haddad, Robert
  - Haff, Heather
  - Hafizovic, Resid
  - Haflich, Clay
  - Hagan, Billy
  - Hagan, Clarence W.
  - Hagberg, James
  - Hageman, Jane
  - Haggerty, Catherine L.
  - Haggerty, Jon
  - Hagruth, Haley
  - Hahn, Dorothy
  - Hailperin, Herman *
  - Hajduk, Tom
  - Hak-Ju, Kim
  - Hakala, Thomas R.
  - Hake, Sabine
  - Hales, Thomas C.
  - Haley, Leon L.
  - Hall, Anna *
  - Hall, Charles *
  - Hall, Deanne
  - Hall, John K., II
  - Hall, John O.
  - Hall, Martica
  - Hall, Mary Ann
  - Hall, Van Beck
  - Hall, W. Keith
  - Hall, Walter
  - Hall, William
  - Hallal, Joe
  - Hallerberg, Mark
  - Halliday, David *
  - Hallis, (Lieutenant Colonel)
  - Hallock, J. W.
  - Hall-Quest, Lawrence, (Prof.)
  - Hallum, J. (Dr.)
  - Halmaghi, John
  - Halperin, Sandra
  - Halpin, Jason
  - Halsey, Luther *
  - Halstein, Theodore
  - Halzman, Albert G.
  - Ham, Clifford C. *
  - Hamburger, Martin A.
  - Hamilton, Alfred Reed (oversize)
  - Hamilton, Andrew D.
  - Hamilton, Calvin S.
  - Hamilton, Howard Britton *
  - Hamilton, Jean (SEE Walls, Jean)
  - Hamilton, John S. (class of 1840)
  - Hamilton, Rebekah
  - Hamilton, Richard Gillespie (Dr.)
  - Hamilton, Thomas J. *
  - Hammer, Sigmund I.
  - Hammermeister, Frieda
  - Hammitt, Edna F.
  - Hammon, William
  - Hammond, Paul Y.
  - Hammond, Peter
  - Hammond, Sara
  - Hamor, William A.
  - Hampton, Carolyn
  - Hampton, David
  - Hampton, Jean E.
  - Hampton, Marian C.
  - Hampton, Moses *
  - Hamstrom, Elvera
  - Handen, Benjamin L.
  - Hanee, Robert T.
  - Hanges, Nicholas
  - Hanhau, Michael *
  - Hanig, Martin (Dr.)
  - Hanin, Israel
  - Hanks, Bryan K.
  - Hanks, William Earl *
  - Hanley, Tullah
  - Hannan, William J. *
  - Hannigan, Jamie
  - Hannigan, Robert L.
  - Hannigan, W. John
  - Hanratty, William
  - Hansen, Susan
  - Hanson, W. E.
  - Hapke, Bruce (Dr.)
  - Happ, Chris
  - Happ, Mary Beth
  - Harbaugh, Jack
  - Harbaugh, John W. *
  - Harbison, S. P. *
  - Harbrecht, Brian G.
  - Hardesty, David
  - Hardesty, Robert L. *
  - Harding, Patrick
  - Hardman, John H.
  - Hardy, Joseph A., Sr.
  - Harger, James H.
  - Harguth, Haley
  - Hariston, Anita
  - Harke, Bruce
  - Harkins, Gerald
  - Harkins, Sue
  - Harland, Susan
  - Harmon, William W.
  - Harner, Alena
  - Harner, Christopher D.
  - Harnish, Thomas I.
  - Harper, John *
  - Harper, Pat
  - Harrell, Tisha
  - Harrer, Carter John
  - Harries, Kent
  - Harrigan, Birney
  - Harrigan, Peter
  - Harriott, Claude
  - Harris, David A.
  - Harris, E. Lynn
  - Harris, Earl
  - Harris, Eddy L.
  - Harris, Jack (oversize)
  - Harris, Jane Gary
  - Harris, Jonathan
  - Harris, Joseph